# John Bergsen

123 W Adams Ave, Detroit, MI 12345 youremail@exannple.com (123) 456-7890

Audio-Video Technician with 5+ years of advancement and experience. Skilled at putting complex technical topics in clear, accessible terms for lay audiences. Natural collaborator who builds productive relationships with clients and colleagues. Focused on finding new ways to raise organization efficiency and service quality.

## Key Skills

- Audio & Video Technology
- Complex Problem-Solving
- Cross-Functional Collaboration
- Equipment Monitoring & Troubleshooting
- Internal & External Client Relations
- · Inventory Management
- Meeting & Event Facilitation
- Preventative Maintenance
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Process Improvement
- Video Conferencing

## **Professional Experience**

#### Audio-Video Technician

LMN Company, Inc., Detroit, MI I February 2021 to Present

- Set up and monitored equipment, including cameras, monitors, and speakers
- Introduced new standard procedures that helped streamline equipment setup operations, raising efficiency by 26%
- Raised average customer satisfaction rate by 12 points to 95%

#### Manager

QRS Stores, Detroit, MI j April 2020 to February 2021

 Gained a strong sense of teamwork and collaboration overseeing a top-ranked, 10-person group at this retail location

#### Audio-Video Technician

MNO Company, Inc., Detroit, MI j April 2017 to April 2020

- Expedited average equipment setup and takedown times by 18%
- Established due diligence protocols that improved service quality
- Demonstrated early leadership by taking on a mentor role for newly hired technicians

### Education

Bachelor of Science (BS) - Video Broadcasting

University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, MI, 2017